Worked on the series:
Lily, Tiramisu, Pineapple, Zinger, Biryulka
How did I become
queen
FANSUB GROUP AZALIA PRESENTS
No, that's not what I meant!
We'll have to take the extreme step.
And he's fast.
-What is this?
- I have to ask you this.
While I was drinking, I thought that the moonlight would be enough for my mood,
So I blew out the candle.
I wanted to stretch my throat before I started drinking for real.
You can consider this a warm-up.
So, what?
What are you doing? Damn it.
Wasn't it you who wanted to warm each other's throats?
What a smart asshole. Did he do it on purpose?
No, it's impossible.
Since we've warmed our throats,
start drinking heartily, my queen.
Where?
One person is not interesting.
Somehow I didn't think about it.
I'll pour it.
Thank you for the warm-up welcome,
Now the wine went smoothly.
What? What did I do?
Here, have a drink.
You must drink too, my queen.
The king drinks first.
No, the queen drinks first.
Changed strategy.
I know your dark thoughts.
Then let's have a glass
and to bed, fortunately it was a long day.
What are you saying? Yes, we have just begun.
Don't be like that.
Come on. One salvo for my health.
In one gulp.
I'm a light sleeper
so stay away while we sleep.
What kind of game was he playing with such nonsense?
Blooms during the day, withers at night.
These tales about the king's love for alcohol and women...
Chronicles about Joseon lie like the yellow press.
I shouldn't have been scared.
But we must not let down our guard.
Finally using it
a woman's knot, which I learned in the army.
If he wants to untie it, he will have to cut it.
Frets.
Damn selfish.
Took up the whole bed.
Sorry, my queen.
I understand your feelings
but today I just want to sleep.
Everything is wrong. I was raised in comfort
I can't sleep on the bare floor.
Give me one.
I can't sleep
less than three feather beds.
I'm sure your comfort cannot compare with the royal one.
This lumberjack prince from Ganghwa
Obviously I didn’t study history.
Christmas trees.
To break his sleep paralysis.
Since things turned out this way,
I'll be on guard all night.
For some reason today I still remember the army.
Episode 2: Nobody Knows
Are you awake, Your Majesty?
Here's an ambush.
I hoped not, but I'm still here.
What is it like to greet a new day as a queen?
Shitty.
There you go.
My woman's knot.
Lost something again?
-I'll search everything...
-No!
I'm sure he untied it at night and got in the way, I suppose. So?
Your Majesty.
When did you arrive in Hijeongjong?
Sorry for not accompanying you.
I didn’t want to wake the queen and quietly left.
Are you having nightmares again?
She shouldn't lose sleep over me.
It's her first day as queen.
I will bring you Arabic jasmine tea and you will sleep well tonight.
The Queen must now be greeting the ladies of the court.
I heard they've already left.
I wonder what the queen looks like now.
The wedding was yesterday
Why didn’t I wake up in time, how are things going again?
You should go and greet
the Queen Dowager and the Queen Mother
and hold a festive ceremony for the court officials.
After the official part of the wedding ceremony...
When will the wedding end?
No, then His Majesty must read the message
about your proclamation as queen.
Some kind of endless wedding.
Just a minute. So the Queen Dowager is...
This is the Queen Dowager's order.
I'll fill the lake with water -
I will go against her orders.
What kind of person is the Queen Dowager?
Dowager Queen
like you, from the Andon clan Kim, she is an elder,
and the queen mother is from the Pungyang Cho family.
So my acquired granny and mommy are at enmity.
And I, the queen, am of the same kind as grandma.
Can I ask her when I see her?
The older one is the Queen Dowager.
What else?
It’s really important to me, will you tell me everything you know?
She is Mr. Kim Jwageun's sister
and has not left the palace since she arrived.
-Also...
-Stop.
I'm talking about the palanquin. Stop!
-Stop!
-Stand.
Back.
Roll it back.
Like this.
Something more important has emerged here.
Got lost because the palace is too big?
Nice to meet you. What's your name?
That's it.
I will never get used to this body.
You have such an attractive aura.
Are you from the royal family too?
Is there some kind of princess there?
My apologies.
If I was arrogant and upset you,
Please forgive me.
No. What I'm trying to say...
Your Majesty.
You walk so fast. How did you get here?
Hello.
Do you know her?
This is Lady Hwajin of the Cho family,
future royal concubine.
I understand that the queen
but didn't she insult you too much?
Continues to play with words.
Rumor has it that she
pushed you into the lake.
I am sure that the rumor about the queen losing her memory is a lie.
-Be careful.
I've met so many women
that I can easily read their faces.
You... How should I say this?
Good man.
I guess we didn't work out in the past
so maybe we can start again?
I like you.
Let's be friends.
Have you decided to change tactics?
Tactics?
Thanks to you I learned
what is the palace like?
I was finally able to understand that I am now also a part of it.
No, it looks like you misunderstood me.
-It's not like that.
-Sorry, I have to go.
Your Majesty!
-Your Majesty.
I came to your chambers
but you weren't there.
I wanted to greet you too, but I couldn’t find you.
This is how we must have missed each other
because our thoughts converge.
If she's a concubine
So it turns out that she is considered a second wife?
Why this body?
Why this?
The fire in the queen's eyes can burn the fields.
Rent yourself a room already!
My queen
please tell me as soon as possible
to the royal concubine what and how.
What a shame!
I don't have time to explain everything to her here.
This is the king's order.
Fuck polygamy.
Your Majesty!
The queens have been waiting for you for so long!
I have a very important meeting, I'll go.
What the hell is this?
Your Majesty!
I was very scared
Hwajin?
Finally I can call you my wife.
Now we will live together in the palace.
You deserve a real wedding ceremony
but the eunuch saw you not far from the lake.
Officials are trying
blame you for what happened.
So I had to speed up the selection.
I was at the lake because I was scared
hearing a loud sound.
Don't worry.
She can't hurt you
no matter what family she comes from.
No, not like that.
I will do everything to keep you safe.
I will protect you with all my might.
Your Majesty.
Unfortunately, I have
there aren't many ways to do this.
I'm just a puppet on a throne.
But I have a brother who cares about me
and a friend who would do anything for fun.
And also
wonderful woman.
Yes, you are rich.
I explained to the officials where you were.
Don't worry.
What? Well, which one is the widowed granny?
Bow to the Queen Dowager, Your Majesty.
Never mind, walk away flaw.
I hope you slept soundly, Queen Dowager.
You have become so much younger this night!
You can't tell how old you are.
You almost fooled me, Your Majesty.
Scoundrel.
Is it true?
So it’s not in vain that I’m trying so hard.
Good job, Jang Bong Hwan, keep it up.
A great misfortune has happened to you.
What a horror it seems
you haven't fully recovered yet.
What nonsense are you talking about?
We couldn't have found a better queen!
Just as sharp-tongued as ever.
Right.
I looked closer and I see.
They smile so sweetly, but in reality
They would rip each other's throats out.
Full combat readiness.
Now you have to do your best
try to produce an heir.
At one time I found out
effective way to do this
so that a little prince will definitely be born.
Don't torment us.
Imagine spending the night with your spouse.
He lies on his back
and you on top...
Give her the "Best Mother-in-Law" award.
This is a very important point
climb on top and...
Mother, I can handle this very well myself!
Just shut up, I beg you.
Well, let's just say I studied the literature carefully.
Smart girl!
How many things have you learned?
to become a wonderful wife.
I'm sure you are well aware.
I agree,
I'm sorry I crossed the line.
This means that the daughter-in-law should be more modest,
and the grandson’s wife has to figure something out.
What a nightmare!
Not sleeves, but murder weapons!
My neck is cracking.
You must be very tired.
No wonder
We had too much to drink last night.
What did we drink there?
The courtiers are already waiting for us.
I suggest you hurry up.
Injeongjeong Hall
State Councilor Kim Byung-hak.
Congratulations.
Left advisor Kim Seok-keun.
Minister of War Kim Chang-hyuk.
Congratulations.
And all the Kims.
So that's what you are like,
the famous trio of Kims from Andong.
With the help of the Queen Dowager and the King's wife
they came up with
various pretexts for collecting taxes.
Because of them, the people suffered greatly.
In my time
they were accused of corruption in the defense sector
and real estate,
as well as tax evasion.
Our arrows have ripened everywhere.
In other words, here it is, a trio of bastards,
a symbol of the corruption that has destroyed the country.
Andon clan Kim.
Right advisor Man-heon Cho.
Congratulations.
Minister of Officials Cho Dongmoon.
And here is the Cho family from Pungyang.
These are famous for holding
closer to the Queen Mother.
When her son Hongjong was king,
they were held in high esteem, and then he passed away.
Kim So-yeon from the Andong family ascended the throne,
and they lost their influence.
Now they are just small fish.
The one who really means something is...
Troop commander Kim Jwageun.
My congratulations, Your Majesty,
Your Majesties.
Here he is - the man
in whose hands is all the power of the Kim family.
Since we are here about your wedding,
I would like to report something.
Speak.
Head of the Royal Guard
is responsible for your safety.
I advise you to schedule this
position of Kim Moon-geun.
My father-in-law?
Right.
This is a very important post.
The Queen is concerned about your safety.
I apologize for not mentioning this earlier.
Is this what you wished for?
God knows, but
I will stick with the winners.
Am I alive or dead
I will be concerned about your safety.
To make sure you are safe and healthy,
I didn't sleep all night.
A snake, not a woman.
That's it, then I agree.
Dowager Queen
I was glad to hear about the queen's request.
My brother currently holds this position.
Prince Yeonpyeong.
I need time to think.
Your safety comes first.
Your Majesty, please make a decision
ASAP.
Your love for me knows no bounds.
Then, with your permission, I will continue.
Kim Jwageun,
a person whose power exceeds that of the king.
That's who really rules the country.
This would be a place for a popcorn.
-Your Majesty!
-Queen!
Sorry, let's continue the event.
It looks like the queen is tired.
We'll probably end here.
The night together is the time when the gods
help to conceive an heir.
We should not indulge in pleasures.
However, last night I was impatient.
There is nothing wrong with being happily married.
How's that?
What is he talking about here?
Let's leave it at that then.
-Thank you, Your Majesty.
You were bluffing, weren't you?
I don't understand you.
There was nothing last night.
You upset me, yes, you drank a lot,
but how could you forget
what happened on your wedding night?
What are you talking about?
I understand everything.
You've damaged your memory
you may forget about something.
That can't be true.
There was nothing between us.
You have been verified.
Check? What kind of check?
Virginity check,
there was blood on the bed.
I have something to do, I'll go.
Wait a minute! We didn't agree!
Your Majesty, let's go to the chambers.
Don't worry, Jang Bong Hwan, he's lying.
Think for yourself, you would know if something happened.
There was nothing! Nothing!
Naturally he doesn't want
so that the people know that he is not hardy.
And he seems to like to twist the truth.
And it doesn't matter!
Do you have to be so calculating?
What the hell is this about checking?
What is this for?
Wait a minute!
May I ask a question?
The girl will know if something happened?
Something?
What are you talking about, Your Majesty?
This one is too young.
And this one holds celibacy worse than monks.
Looks like none of you can answer me.
What a nightmare!
-Is the child crying because of me?
-Of course not, Your Majesty.
The wind is cold. Let me close the window.
-I’m already sweating myself.
-Very cold.
-It's hot here!
-Catch a cold.
I'm hot!
Let's go.
I can't stop thinking about Cheoljong's words.
Eat in peace, Your Majesty.
Seeing the queen
I realized that she was still not herself.
How should I say it?
Overly arrogant?
She was always brave
but not so arrogant and fearless.
She lost her composure during the ceremony.
I have to teach her some decency.
You can't show your weakness to others.
And as for Cho Hwajin...
Are you sure she was with His Majesty that night?
Yes, I made sure of this.
She entered the palace 15 minutes later
after an accident.
This is not proof that she tried to harm Her Majesty,
but you can try to use it.
Big mystery.
If she didn't do it, then who?
Do you think anyone else is involved?
Maybe.
It doesn't matter who exactly did it.
The more important thing is who we need to blame for this.
Who do we need?
If we point to a deer
and let's say it's a horse, then it will be a horse.
In our case, the deer can actually become a horse.
Fine. Forget about business for a while
and eat, Your Majesty.
Since you make sure I eat well,
I have to take care of my health.
I won't let anyone harm you.
Bon appetit.
"I hereby confer senior rank within the court
Cho Hwajin, daughters
court secretary Cho Daesu from the Pungyang Cho family.
She was also given the title of royal concubine
for her beauty and righteousness."
Pungyang Cho family.
Their families are feuding, just like them.
Did she really push Kim So-yeon into the lake?
She's dangerous
and that's what attracts me.
I am grateful to you, Your Majesty.
Let's be friends.
I'm on the winning side, of course,
but I can’t resist such a beauty.
Let's be friends.
You'll soon understand that I
sheer perfection, well, except
a couple of shortcomings.
Since we've gotten so close,
can I ask a question?
There is no one else to ask.
I'm not sure if I have the wisdom to answer the question.
You definitely know everything about him. I'm talking about the king.
Does he often lie?
I've heard a lot about him.
And they say the king
disappears at night.
Does it disappear at night?
I haven't heard anything like that.
A fighter by day, and disappeared by night.
He said it was like we had a hot night together.
-He tends to distort...
-Your Majesty.
With all due respect, this is highly inappropriate.
Sorry if I offended you. I can't help but think about it.
I just arrived yesterday, I have a lot on my mind.
Sorry for taking up time. Go.
See you.
I will say one thing for sure. His Majesty is not like that.
Not like that? Are you saying he's not lying?
Or doesn't it disappear at night? What are you talking about?
It couldn't be clearer!
Crap.
Robbers!
Robbers! There are robbers here!
Robbers! They're there!
Robbers!
Don't cry. No need.
Stop it, okay?
My baby, baby!
No!
Your Majesty.
There was no secret storage either, I checked it at night.
I searched thoroughly
all the hidden corners in the palace,
is it possible that this is hidden in the tiger's den?
Your Majesty, the queen is here to see you.
I'm too busy with the affairs of the country.
So am I on the case.
There's a lot to talk about.
So busy you keep it upside down.
This is not without reason, I thought about a lot of things.
Think out your thoughts. I'll wait.
And why are you staring like that?
You see,
It's interesting to see how hard you try.
As a king, I must oversee the affairs of the country.
Is he talking about “business” on purpose?
I have appointed a royal concubine as you wished.
You can sleep in your chambers.
With pleasure.
Is there anything you want to tell me?
You came to me yourself.
You probably want to say something yourself.
Since it's just the two of us here, let's be honest.
Last night we...
We had a great time.
Okay, if you keep pretending...
Lord.
You're distracting me.
If you don't want to talk,
do we use hand signals?
For example, this one.
What is this?
This means that I'm lying about everything.
What do you say? It's not difficult, is it?
The king never lies.
You can go.
Crap. So infuriating.
With a straight face he insists that something happened.
Was it true or not?
Your Majesty, was it a hard day?
Oh, it tickles.
Hey, take it easy.
I'm ticklish.
Your Majesty.
Etiquette classes start today.
My behavior is already in order.
This is a crash course in palace etiquette.
Don't want.
Order from the Queen Dowager.
I want to go back
and not pass the test.
First, I will defeat the queen.
You may not know it, but I studied etiquette
in Cheongaktong for four years.
Show how well-mannered the graduate is?
The royal woman is as calm as Buddha.
It does not create a breeze while walking.
The candle lights do not flicker.
She doesn't open her mouth wide when eating.
and does not bite off in large pieces.
Embroidery is the best way for a woman
sort out your thoughts.
Embroidery. She can do it.
I'm well brought up.
Can't I breathe now?
It's worse here than in Cheongaktong.
Fuck it.
How to eat such beauty?
First, watch and enjoy.
Are we watching? Looks like
you stuff everything into your mouth.
You used to like it.
Hongyong, try it. Wider your mouth.
What happened, Your Majesty?
Is this Kim So-yeon's memories?
Heart...
Poisoned.
Get the doctor here quickly!
-Your Majesty.
-Spit it out.
-It's not pain.
Is this woman in love with Cheoljong?
You must love me.
His eyes.
This is more than hatred. He despises her.
Please, Your Majesty.
I like snacks more than alcohol itself.
And good.
All alcohol is in your favor.
He wasn't going to share this night with me.
So he tried to get me drunk.
We were thinking the same thing.
Now you have to do your best
try to produce an heir.
Come to your senses, Your Majesty.
Bring water!
To fool the Kim family
forcing them to sleep,
Cheoljong lied.
Hongyeon. There was nothing!
Thinking about this almost drove me crazy.
I trust myself, but not that idiot.
However...
What are you doing here?
-More. Pull it up higher.
-Yes.
That's how tiring it is to maintain your position.
Decrepancy means you have become weaker.
If you do this twice a day,
wrinkles will not get deeper.
It's clear. You try so hard.
Why did you come to me?
At your insistence, having received etiquette lessons,
I realized what I should do
a real queen.
I'm very happy.
- Enough, stop.
-Okay, okay.
So, yesterday we went to bed with His Majesty,
but it’s like all the strength has been pumped out of me,
I became all so lethargic.
I kept wondering what the reason was, and I understood!
This is because the reservoirs have been drained.
That’s why my feminine principle has weakened.
If only they were filled with water again,
I would immediately carry the prince.
Excluded.
- Damn it.
-We barely saved you.
In a good way, everyone who allowed
something like this should happen, he should be executed.
However, on the eve of such a happy event,
we showed mercy and did not shed blood.
But since you want to fill the ponds
water, all those responsible will have to be punished.
Who was there? Hongyong,
court lady Choi. Who else?
All those involved will be punished with all severity.
What a wicked one. This is not your sweet neighbor's grandmother.
What if I perform
marital duty for three whole nights,
to conceive a son for the king as soon as possible?
Will you fill the ponds with water for this?
Seven nights.
Five.
Listen here. Everyone who was involved...
Seven nights.
Seven is a good number.
If you promise to fill the ponds with water,
I will do everything to conceive a prince.
Even a little boy, even a little dog, just to come back.
Concubine Cho has come to greet you.
Wow, you're so attractive
and graceful, just as they describe you.
His Majesty has an eye for beauties.
You flatter me.
This is a gift.
Something you'll need in the palace.
There is no way to do this without this.
Take a look.
Life in the palace is not at all easy.
There is no one to rely on here.
Here you can forget about quiet days.
Oh yes, tell me which one
day and year you were born?
Do you know what to do
to conceive a son for His Majesty?
What am I talking about?
First you need to check
compatibility with His Majesty.
Contact me if you need a powerful talisman.
I know a shaman who knows
the use of evil eyes and curses.
Last time I was very pleased with her.
Your Majesty, please forgive me.
But I'm here to
care for the good of His Majesty.
Apparently I misunderstood something.
Sorry, Queen Mother.
Perhaps I expressed myself too harshly.
Everything is fine. Don't take it to heart.
By the way, about the heart. These are your first days in the palace,
and you will have to vegetate alone.
What a shame. What are you planning to do?
What?
For the next seven days His Majesty will
sleep in Her Majesty's chambers.
After all, everything is fine with them anyway,
peace and quiet.
So they will spend seven more nights together.
But you don't have to worry.
I am sure that during these seven days the feelings of His Majesty
they won't cool down on you.
Someday you too will lose
person dear to you.
Madam.
Looks like I ruined the sheet
there is nothing to fix here.
It's a pity, but I'll have to write everything again.
You are so beautiful that you could easily become a queen.
The only advantage the queen has is a good pedigree,
and she spins His Majesty as she wants.
Remember.
The queen has the same status as the king.
Remember, the higher the status, the greater the responsibility,
watch what you say.
Don’t go to a fortune teller here, it’s her doing.
It was she who whispered to the ladies of the court about seven nights.
She also accused you of something you didn’t do.
What a shame that you ended up there
at the most inopportune moment!
I haven’t gotten used to life in the palace yet.
My tongue is my enemy.
Forgive me, madam.
How can I earn His Majesty's favor?
She herself told me to spend the night in my chambers.
And then she turned to the dowager queen
with a completely different request.
How difficult it is to understand a lady's heart.
Listen, I want something for you
suggest. You don't mind, do you?
How can I refuse you?
I suggest sticking to social distancing.
-No really.
-You said that you wouldn’t refuse.
I don't understand the meaning of your words.
Didn’t understand anything, but already gave up?
That's why I refused because I didn't understand anything.
Well then listen, I’ll explain now.
Social distancing -
This is when everyone is on their own.
Which is very good.
Let's say we kind of have to sleep together.
In fact, you sleep at your place, and I sleep at mine.
This is distancing.
I'm still against it.
But why?
I don't know why, but I don't like it.
What a damn pervert.
Well, you need to speak to perverts in their own language.
You know, I don't remember anything from last night.
Maybe we can repeat it?
Let's light it up properly.
Shall we light it?
Let's have a hot night.
Tonight
it will be our first time.
Well then...
What are you doing? Come on quickly. They'll notice you.
It was not proper for a king to sneak around like a thief.
What a moron.
What? Court Lady Choi?
We could be in big trouble, Your Majesty.
How can I become a good ruler?
what if I don’t know how ordinary people live?
May your thoughts be noble
the idea is still too dangerous.
Of course, I’m ready to give my life for you, but still...
Where's the map?
-This time...
-Name plate?
I should stop you.
It turns out that my name is
Lee Sanman?
What is this creepy name?
Sen as "to contemplate" and Man as "as to "try".
A contemplator who tries for the good
people. You can't think of a better name.
Well, let's say. That's not my name and that's okay.
-When does the curfew start there?
-At the hour of the mouse
the guards ring the bells 28 times,
and then the gates are closed.
The bells are ringing, that is?
At the hour of the mouse?
It sucks. The hour when all the fun begins.
Well, nothing.
I promise to be back by then.
Well, no.
I'll do anything
but I won’t let you leave.
Hongyeon.
What kind of person am I anyway?
you always
kind and cheerful.
Extremely friendly
and always very smiling.
You understand that I better know
the truth from you than from someone else.
It's true.
OK.
So, one day you were reading a book.
It's simply impossible to read here!
You're breathing so noisily
that I will soon go deaf!
Come here! Take him away and give him a good spanking!
I have long-term problems with my nose.
Have mercy, Your Highness!
Let's go.
You're off by one fourth note.
Did the bear step on your ear or what?
And you still call yourself a teacher?
Come here!
Flog this idiot!
Is it true? It can't be!
Is it funny to you?
Apparently there is nothing to do.
Come here! Take these two away and give them a good beating!
Just one breath
and you are already losing your temper.
It's worth putting on perfume
accused of trying to seduce the king.
We walk noisily - it’s bad,
We walk silently - it’s even worse.
You will always find something to complain about.
Every little thing makes you angry.
That's why they called you a viper.
Oh, sorry.
I just wanted to fill you in on the details,
but I got a little carried away.
It looks like a lot of people wanted to drown this girl.
So that's why the ladies of the court...
They just don't know who you really are.
Do you know?
Of course.
I have been serving you since childhood.
And I know that your heart is good.
And that you are smart beyond your years.
And since you have something in mind,
you will certainly achieve your goal.
You are an example for me.
Although you are often in the palace
feel lonely.
After all, His Majesty is after every skirt.
This lady was not so lonely.
Once there was a person nearby who understood her so well.
Lady?
This means that you brighten up my loneliness.
What are you talking about?
Don't worry, Hongyeon. Get a good night's sleep.
For your sake, I will try not to get caught.
I will kill you all!
Better take your other eye, you bastards!
I won't let you take my wife and child away like some kind of slaves!
If you don't pay taxes,
then give them to us!
This scoundrel is still a sinner!
My only sin is
Let a child live in such a terrible world!
Don't come any closer! Don't come near me.
This madman is guilty of treason!
If killing scoundrels like you is treason, I will do it.
Yes! I'll be happy to do this!
Expensive!
Don't do this.
I know you're upset.
These scoundrels want us dead.
Why should I stop?
Damhyang.
Make way! Out of the way! Make way!
What's going on here?
What should we do?
Father, you are back.
Yes, how was your trip?
Sorry I missed it
such a joyful event.
Have you made your decision?
What are you leaning towards?
I decided to follow my dream.
But how far I'll go, I don't know yet.
How far?
Right.
I trust you and won't rush you.
But something happened in your absence.
The queen fell into the lake
the night before the wedding.
She was unconscious all day
so the wedding had to be postponed.
How is Her Highness now?
Is she okay?
Stand!
I haven't seen you before.
Judging by the way you're looking around...
-Well...
-First time in the palace?
Apparently lost.
I also got lost for the first time.
This is true.
But you look somehow familiar.
Expensive clothes
and unshakable self-confidence.
Must be from a noble family.
I was going to say the same thing.
You are that famous son.
Attractive and from a respected family.
Smart and talented.
I've heard about you. Your name...
Kim Hwan
from the Andon clan Kim.
Here are those on, her relative.
Am I that famous?
Certainly.
Ask anyone on the street: everyone knows.
Such an honor to meet you.
I was about to go out too.
Let's go together.
I came from the other side.
It's dark, so I got it wrong.
Blow and he's killed.
How can you talk so much?
He didn't pause for a second.
That's why it's a little creepy here.
And that's why His Majesty has nightmares every night.
Nightmares?
Since His Majesty returned from Ganghwa,
he has the same nightmare every night.
About
how he is accused of treason
and beheaded.
We apologize that we didn't recognize you.
Not scary. So many people
pass through this gate.
Lee Sanman
On the occasion of our acquaintance, I would like
visit the kisen's house.
Which one is the best?
Oktajeong. This one is the best.
Girls laugh like this
when you mention the jade tablet. Therefore, Oktajeong.
Show me the way.
Look how bright the moon is.
A great night to have fun.
Here.
Let's go.
-Easy work.
-Yes.
It seems we're the same age
and our hobbies are similar. I'm so glad we met.
Oh yes. You haven't told me your name yet.
What's your name?
I'm Lee Senman.
Lee Saengman as "Loser in this life."
Don't blame me!
What's your name?
Yes, that's it.
My apologies.
You are a woman.
What are you talking about? I'm definitely a man.
We do not serve women.
Girls, greet the young master!
Like this!
It's a great honor to meet you.
Let me pour you...
I don't drink more than three cups of wine a day.
I've already drunk two
and I want to share the last one with my friend.
He doesn't change his mind.
His son recently passed the civil servant's exam.
Congratulations.
Although he is capable,
he was unable to get a good position in Hanyang.
If you can help him, I will gladly pay you,
how much do you say?
You're asking me to sell
the position of a government official for money?
Well, I meant...
I just wanted to express my gratitude.
I know your son passed the exam a long time ago.
-Why did you come now?
-Well, I...
You first contacted the Pungyang Cho family.
My wife is their distant relative.
Please forgive me.
I understand your feelings
about your smart and capable son who couldn't
achieve what you want because of family mistakes.
I will help him clear his name and become the king's secretary.
Royal secretary?
Thank you. Thank you so much!
And you don't have to pay me.
I need a friend in return.
The one who will be ready to give his life for me.
From now on my whole family will be
It's a pleasure to serve you, sir.
Pour me some wine.
Now we are friends.
Yes! Thank you.
Well, now let's go!
We'll drink until we fall over.
Let's let go of worries and have a lot of fun!
Ladies' man!
And don't forget about me!
-How good!
-Look here!
Here, have a drink.
-It's another matter.
-Fine.
Mister!
You are so handsome!
And which of you will have the honor
Should you undress me at night?
I've been a pussy for 20 years now,
I’ve never met such a pervert before.
-Here, have a drink.
-Come on, whatever you are.
This is terrible.
I can't believe that in such a place
we drink alone.
This is not the time to complain about this.
We thought he was in a secret vault, but it's empty.
Then there is only one option left.
In the house of the queen's father.
But they want to appoint him as commander of the royal guard,
This means it will be even more difficult to get through.
They want to control the royal guards
so that the king's life would be in their hands.
Then the disguised guards will soon be revealed.
Yes? This is a very dangerous situation.
If they are caught and released, then
haunt at night
corrupt officials
and climb through storage facilities
looking for accounting books
you and I will have to.
That is, during the day I will be an official,
and at night as a mercenary?
Yes, I'll get stuck from overexertion.
You called me from Ganghwado to plow like a horse?
On the way to Hanyang
I was full of ambition and great dreams.
“I will use a friend and succeed.”
I said I want to save our decaying, corrupt country
and you decided to follow suit.
You didn't say that.
They constantly talked about Khanyan, so I asked.
And this is what you answered:
Why Hanyang?
Joseon is rotting. I want to teach these scoundrels a lesson!
Right.
Sounded great
but I didn’t know that I would have to bend my back like that.
I was an idiot.
Do you think you've changed a lot?
Maybe they want to take control of the guards,
because you understood what we were up to?
Come on.
If that were the case they would have sent someone here
eavesdrop on us.
Exactly.
Kick inconvenient.
Where's the toilet?
And here he is.
(Women's restroom, men's restroom)
Huh?
Hey.
I envy you.
I had it too.
And now it’s gone.
Farewell my dragon.
Bye-bye, dragon.
I can't even relieve myself standing.
Pig world, such pleasure is available only to those who have it.
How terribly sad, I really didn’t want to write.
Even the tears have dried up.
And the dragon is no longer there.
And dragon balls too.
It's easier to die already.
Atrocity. Why is this happening to me? For what?
-Pour a glass.
-Here.
How great.
Ass?
Do you think they realized that blood
was there actually a pig on the marriage bed?
Since they want to give the queen's father this position,
This means they have no idea about us.
Otherwise
your heads would already be lying on the ground.
Then why suddenly...
All that has changed is the queen
and the royal concubine together in the palace.
The Queen will want to keep her under control.
Puts a sword to her husband's neck immediately after the wedding?
Creepy girl.
Considering what happened,
You need to stop searching for a while.
We are getting ready
to a righteous war against the authorities.
The only way to punish them is
find papers that confirm corruption.
They use double entry system, we can't
postpone searching for books.
What should we do then?
Let him take the position of commander of the royal guard.
-But!
-If we throw the bait,
they will attack her
and they won’t even notice what’s really happening.
He will be absorbed in his new position,
this will help you find the accounting books.
As for the position, we can take it,
when he thinks that she is his.
It's difficult to defend our positions
but getting them back will be even more difficult.
Only a real warrior will lead the guard.
I understand that he will be a simple puppet,
but he won't succeed
unless he is physically able to do the job.
Let's make a little incident on his first day.
And if Kim Moon-geun is smarter than we think,
and will understand who the guards really are?
Let's make sure the royal guard is protected,
and get the books.
Let's go to extreme measures.
If you already know how, then why not now?
What is a "last resort"?
Assassination attempt.
It will happen anyway.
What a sad little room?
Oh, you!
The bell is ringing!
Was it the queen?
Was she spying on us dressed as a man?
We can't let her go.
We don't even know what she heard.
I'm sure there's someone else here with her.
So, you need to catch up with her and close your mouth.
Your Majesty.
Don't let your emotions get in your way.
I'll figure it out myself.
10.
11.
Damn, this is where I'll end up if I don't get back on time.
Your Majesty, don't trust anyone.
Be especially careful with those who are close.
You know who did it.
The criminal is...
If the queen heard everything,
bloodshed is inevitable.
Who are you?
How dare the girl come here?
When I'm here
I'm the boss.
Are you holding it like this?